wdmtech.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy

WDM Tech is sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet. Although generally a User is under no obligation to provide personal information while accessing the Site, there are some circumstances under which a User may be asked to provide such information.

#### Information Collection and Use

In some circumstances, We may request personal information from the User, such as his or her name, e-mail address, company name, telephone number, etc. Users are free to respond or not to respond to these inquiries; all information provided to us is strictly voluntary. WDM Tech is the sole owner of information collected by this Site. We will not sell, share or rent this information to third parties.  
We allow Users to submit their resumes online. Any resume received by us will be held in confidence and used only for the purpose of considering the submitting party for employment. Such information is not shared with any third parties or external agencies.Some areas of this Site may require Users to provide personal information in order to complete certain functions. Such functions may not be available to Users who choose not to provide the information requested.

#### Use of Log Files

Algoworks collects User domain information in order to analyze the use of this Site. This data enables us to become more familiar with who visits our Site, how often they visit and what parts of the Site they visit most often. We use this information to improve its Web-based offerings. This information is collected automatically and requires no action by the User. By accessing our Site, Users grant their unconditional consent to allow us to collect their domain names.

#### Use of Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the User's hard drive that contains information about the User. By using a cookie on the Algoworks Site, a User does not have to log into the Site using a password more than once. Cookies also enable Algoworks to track and target the interests of our Users in order to enhance their experience on our Site. Using a cookie while on the Algoworks Site does not provide us with the User's personal information. Once the User closes his or her browser, the cookie simply terminates. If a User rejects the cookie, he or she may still access the Algoworks Site. However, the User may experience usage limitations in some areas of the Site.

#### Links

Site contains links to other websites. Please be aware that Algoworks is not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Site. We encourage our Users to read the privacy statements of each website they visit when leaving this Site.

#### Security

We take every precaution to protect a User's information. When Users submit sensitive information via the Site, their information is protected both online and offline.

In addition to using SSL encryption to protect sensitive User information online, We also take extensive measures to protect User information offline. All User information (including non-sensitive data) is restricted to the our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific task (e.g., billing clerks, customer service representatives, etc.) are granted access to Users' personally identifiable information. If you have any questions about the security of this Site, please [Contact us](http://www.wdmtech.com/Contact-Us)

#### Site and Service Updates

We reserve the right to distribute Site and service announcements to Users. Members are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the User's requested services. We communicate with Users via email or phone to provide requested services and to resolve issues relating to their accounts. We reserve the right to modify or update the privacy statement at any time without notice.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy.

We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will notify you of substantial changes to this Policy either by posting a prominent announcement on our site and/or by sending a message to the e-mail address you have provided to us that is contained within your user settings.

#### No guarantees

While this Privacy Policy states our standards for maintenance of Data and we will make efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of Data.
